evilmilk.com 2019-06-19

# Funny Pictures | EvilMilk

**Terms and Conditions:**

You do not require an account to view evilmilk, however some areas of the site you will gain extra priveledges in having one. You must be 18 years or older to create an account on evilmilk. Evilmilk reserves the right to delete users or block acces to any user for any reason.

By submitting content to evilmilk you grant us the right to alter/edit them and post them on the site. Evilmilk reserves the right to not use any submission or reject any for any reason. Evilmilk may or may not place advertising on the pages where your submitted content is viewable. The way evilmilk uses the image can change without any notice.

You are solely responsible for your own content submissions. Byt submitting content you are agreeing that you own the necessary licenses, permissions, trademarks and you are passing that permission on to evilmilk to display the content submitted. By submitting you are affirming that your post does not infringe on any copyrights or the privacy of any person or entity..

By submitting content you retain all licensing and rights to the content. However you are giving evilmilk and its parent company Ceymour Interactive Inc a non exclusive, royalty free, sub-licensable and transferable license to reproduce, copy, change, distribute, store, subliscense to other parties, display, print and use in any other way the submitted content.

Evilmilk does not control user posts. Evilmilk is not responsible for monitoring user posts and it is up to the user to monitor their posts for violations of copyrights or other infringements.

You agree not to modify any parts of the website or attempt to gain access to any parts of the website that are out of the normal bounds. Any password hacking or attempt to hack, SQL injection attempts, transmital of computer viruses or worms can result in blacklisting your account and web address. Any attempt to spider the site or try to hack passwords of other users can result in ban. 

You agree to comply with all applicable local laws, statutes and regulations.

**Content Rules** : violation of these rules can result in the deltion of your posts and or account

You will not post any personal information, either abour yourself or others.

Disruptive posts (Trolling) is not allowed, it is at the discretion of the evilmilk moderators and staff what is considered trolling.

Flooding the site with posts that would hamper the flow of the website or any posts that negatively effect the flow of content on the site will not be allowed.

Misleading or forged content.

You cannot post content that infringes on copyrights, personal rights or proprietary rights of any person or entity.

You may not submit any content that has nudity, unlawful acts, racism, personal information about yourself or anyone else. Do not post content that shows dangerous acts that could harm your safety or the safety of others

Posting any viruses, deceptive posts that could harm users computers or property or anything that purposely harms users or property..

* * *

**Privacy Policy :**

Evilmilk does not distribute this information or use it in any way. All views expressed in this page are matter of opinion and are usually not to be at all taken seriously. This site is meant for entertainment, not education. We do not control what type of content is on the sites we link to. 

**Advertisements**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve the ads displayed on our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email or phone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)

**Linked web sites**   
We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites.

**Children's privacy**   
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems.

Teach kids never to give personal information, unless supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes name, address, phone, school, etc. 

Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites are appropriate. 

Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your child's information is treated. 

Check out the FTC's site ([here](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/topics/protecting-kids-online)) for more tips on protecting children's privacy online.

Return to the latest [funny pictures](https://www.evilmilk.com/)
